You might have heard that your sleep position, whether you're a back, side or stomach sleeper,
can determine the best mattress for you.
While that's a great starting point, it's not always the whole story.
For example, a medium firmness is often best for side sleepers, and a firm mattress is
a solid choice for back or stomach sleepers who need that extra support.
But here's the twist, preferences aren't so predictable.
Some side sleepers swear by firm, while some stomach sleepers love medium.
The truth is, the right mattress is the one that feels best for you.
And at EarthFoam, we're dedicated to helping you find the firmness of your dreams, no matter
what position you sleep in.
If you're not completely satisfied with your purchase, please contact us, and we will work
with you to find a solution that works.